好了  丽芙和玛蒂很快就要考完驾照回家了
Okay, Liv and Maddie will be back from their driving test any second.
准备好庆祝仪式了么
Ready to celebrate?
来看看
Check it.
放声高唱
Sing it loud!
（威斯康星州机动车驾驶执照）
哈  怎样
Bam! What?!
（驾照持有人 丽芙·鲁尼 玛蒂·鲁尼）
我简直等不及我拿到驾照
Ooh, I can't wait to get my license
能随心所欲开车去任何地方的那一刻了
and be able to go wherever I want.
当然在市域范围内
Within the city limits.
在爸妈不准我出门之前
Before my curfew.
开的还是个闻起来像乔伊臭脚的破面包车
In a beat-up minivan that smells like Joey's feet.
还是无比自由啊
Still freedom.
万岁
Whoo-hoo!
这叫自由
Freedom?
这是失去自由好不好
Try loss of freedom.
谁会在无比烦躁还想发短信发到大拇指抽筋
Who wants to drive when you can sit shotgun
的时候专心开车啊
and text until your thumbs fall off?
肯定不是我
Not me.
我真为玛蒂兴奋  拿到了驾照
I'm stoked for Maddie. Having a license...
意味着她可以去任何地方干任何事了
that means she can go anywhere and do anything.
像她这么负责任的青少年一定会
That a responsible teenager would do
先在严父这里得到批准
after getting approval from her father.
我怎么会让她不得到您的恩准就胡作非为呢
Not that I've ever asked her not to get approval.
为什么我还在滔滔不绝呢
Why am I still talking?
为什么你在我房子里呢
Why are you in my house?
为什么你不去理个发呢
Why haven't you gotten a haircut?
我们的问题都不少啊
We've all got questions.
她来了
There she is.
祝贺了  丽芙
Congratulations, Liv.
咱们的两个新司机之一
One of our two new drivers.
先别急着喝彩
Yes. Hold your rah-rahs.
我们中只有一个过了考试
Only one of us passed.
真是倒霉催了啊
Total bummer-rang.
啊  你下次就会拿到驾照了  孩子
Aw, you'll get it next time, kid.
不  我才是过了考试的那个
No. I'm the one who passed.
激动人心吧
License to surprise!
等等  如果你过了  就说明玛蒂没过考试
Wait, if you passed, that means Maddie failed.
玛蒂从来没考过不及格
Maddie doesn't fail anything.
- 哦  - 噢
- Ooh! - Oh!
快烧了  全都烧了
Burn it! Burn it all!
好吧
Well...
我没及格
I failed.
想必我终于知道失败的滋味了
Guess I know what it feels like to be a loser now.
就是乔伊你特别熟悉的那种滋味
You know what I'm talking about, Joey.
哎呀  如果你拿到驾照了
Ouch! I would call that a drive-by...
也算是狗屎运吧
if you had your license.
到底发生了什么
So what happened?
我跟你讲发生了什么吧
I will tell you what happened.
车管所太歧视人了
The DMV discriminates.
（DMV：Department Of Motor Vehicles，车管所)
他们只把驾照发给能够
Yeah. They only give their licenses
完成左转弯的人
to people who can make left-hand turns.
如果你想把车往左开  这招确实有用
They do come in handy when you want to go left.
为啥你要自找没事地开到
Why would you purposefully turn
一堆乱糟糟的车流里而抵达你本需
into oncoming traffic when you can go up one block
右拐三次就能到的地方
and make three rights?
谁这么急着要驾照啊  对不
Who needs their license anyway, am I right?
我啊  我要我的驾照啊
I do! I need my license!
别担心  玛蒂  我会开车带你去你想去的地方的
Don't worry, Maddie. I'll drive you anywhere you want to go.
我怎么还叽里呱啦说个不停啊
Seriously, why am I still talking?
我怎么还站在这里啊
Why am I still here?
我马上去把头发理了
I'll go get my hair cut.